so
you're probably wondering
how the [\h__\h] did I end up here I blame
these guys they baited me with delicious
breakfast food and the next thing you
know
throwing me off a cliff the first match
so in a way
it all started with breakfast
whipped cream and syrup I got a call
from this guy
to meet up with these guys I was already
sold on the food but after meeting the
people and seeing the impact we could
make together it was a done deal
Kodiak goes beyond breakfast they live
differently they're all about getting
outside
[Music]
eating good food
connecting with each other
[Music]
pushing the boundaries and keeping wild
places well wild so yeah when Joel asked
you really want to do this partnership
thing
if I do this
I'm going all in I laid down the goblet
all in so I did
[Music]
and I'm in good company
three two
a handy Brandon Taurus
[Music]
foreign
yeah
very good
[Music]
that was a dying scroll
that was pretty amazing
[Music]
that was amazing